- Nathan?
- Talk to me.
-雷森
-说话
Yes, tonight. Sternwood is doing it tonight.
是的，今晚，斯坦伍德今晚要动手
Jesus, Max, you might finally have got him. Where?
天啊,麦克斯，你最终会捉到他的，在哪里呢？
Aberdeen square.
亚伯丁广场
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
-你确定?
-是的
Yeah, I'm positive.
好的，我己开始行动
Fuck!
干！
Lewinsky?
那人就是莱温斯基？
Max, Sternwood is highly
dangerous. You're obsessed!
麦克斯，斯坦伍德是个高度危险的家伙，你鬼迷心窍啦！
You're not thinking straight!
你从未正经思考过！
Listen to me. Backup is on
its way. Don't go in unarmed.
听俺说，支援已经上路，你别赤膊上阵哈
3 years later
3年后
Repeat: Do not go in unarmed.
That is an order!
重复：你别赤膊上阵哈，这个命令！
Newspaper, Sir?
要看人民日报吗，先生？
Sir? Thank you, Sir.
喂？谢啦，先生。
Newspaper?
人民日报？
- Paper, sir?
- No.
看报纸吗先生？
俺不看那个。
Thank you, Sir.
谢啦，先生。
青年欧茨 布莱克枪击身亡：枪支犯罪激增
Ladies and gentlemen, my name is Joanna
McCauley and I'm your chief flight attendant.
女士们先生们，我是Joanna McCauley，这次航班的首席空服
On behalf of captain Hanna and
the entire crew, welcome aboard...
代表汉纳航空和全体机组，欢迎登机...
...this non-stop flight from
London to Reykjavik.
本航班自伦敦直飞至雷克雅维克（冰岛首都）
Our flight time will be approximately
two hours and 35 minutes.
偶们的航程将近2小时35分钟
We'll be flying at an altitude of 32,000 feet
and a ground speed of 500 miles per hour.
偶们在32,000英尺高度，以最低500英里每小时的速度飞行
Sir, sir, the seat belt sign is-
先森，先森，安全带信号在还未...
- Sir!
- Get out of the way!
-先森！
-死开啦！
- Dad?
- Ruan?
-爸爸？
-鲁安？
I'm so sorry, dad.
抱歉，爸爸
I wouldn't have made it.
我做不到
- Made it back?
- I fucked up.
-你想回来？
-我心乱如麻
What do you mean?
What's wrong?
嘛意思？咋啦？
I fucked up. I have to go
back to the Greigo Mar.
我乱极了，我要回Greigo Mar
Greigo Mar, what's that?
Greigo Mar，是神马？
Stay where you are!
站住！
Look, if you're in some kind of trouble,
嘿，如果你有麻烦
- I can have somebody-
- Dad, I'm scared.
-我会让人...
-爸，我快疯鸟
Lie down on the floor!
给俺趴在地上！
Ruan, where are you?
鲁安，你在哪里？
- Dad-
- Ruan!
-爸...
-鲁安!
Gun crime is an election issue
this morning.
枪支犯罪是今早的竞选话题...
After last night's shooting of
two young men,
昨夜两个年轻人的枪击事件之后
Robert Wiseman, the shadow home secretary...
影子内政大臣罗伯特 魏茨曼
...has again called for the police
force to be fully armed.
再次要求警方全副武装
Max!
麦克斯
We're late.
俺们迟到啦
Again.
又一次了
Wow.
山口山
Place is looking
really homely, Max...
麦克斯，看起来挺像个窝的...
So, Mr. Warns,
沃斯先森
...escorting convoys and guarding v. I.P.S...
重点人人士的押送...
...your days have got to be pretty
regimented, haven't they?
他们把你管过得挺拘束的，不是吗？
Something funny?
很好笑吗？
I'm wise to you.
我只是提醒你
- Yeah? - I can see the path
that you're on.
是么？我看得出你日子不好过
It's like I'm looking at a grid zone.
我好像看到你在笼子里生活
All rolled out in little coordinates.
一点都不和谐嘛
And I'm tracking exactly where
you're going with it.
我看得出你很郁闷啊
I reel off my old routine.
我只是实话实说哈
...like the brainwashed robot
that you think I am.
你看俺像被洗脑了的机器人吧？
And then you tell me how
unfortunate it is that...
你会说你很不幸是因为...
...someone with my conditioning
doesn't know...
像我这般处境的人不了解的是...
.. his exact movements
on Saturday night.
他周六晚上的确切活动
Well, the security guard patrolling the
container yard, said he saw you...
嗯，保安说巡逻到货场时发现了你...
...and a kid fitting the description of Otis
Blake, the night he was murdered.
和一个与描述相符的孩子，在欧茨 布莱克被杀的那晚
That's unfortunate.
真不幸
In fact, he took down
your number plate.
实际上，他记下了你的车牌号
Means you're fucked.
意味着你完蛋了
I wanna told them
and now I'm telling you...
我本想跟他们说的，现在我想对你说
- I was with my grandmother.
- Doing what?
-我是和我奶奶在一起
-干嘛呢？
- I was watching a film.
- What film?
-看电影
-啥电影？
Calamity Jane.
《女侠简恩》
- It is a classic.
- How's that film end again?
-经典片哦
-结局是什么？
They ride off into the
fucking sunset.
他们干到日落
Prick.
鸡鸡
- All right, max?
- All right, mate?
-好啊，麦克斯
-好啊，伙计
They wanna see you.
他们想见你
- Max.
- Nathan. Sir.
-麦克斯
-雷森，长官。
We all good?
都还好吧？
We're letting warns go.
我们准备放了沃茨
The security guard who identified him
at the container yard.
保安在货场认出他了啊
He's retracted his statement.
Says he made a mistake.
他收回了证词，他说搞错了
Warns' grandmother backs up his
alibi, says she was with him all night.
沃茨的奶奶证实了他不在场，说她整晚都和他一起
- Watched a film Calamity Jane.
- This is bullshit.
-看《女侠简恩》
-狗P ！
I need this arrest more than anyone, but
without hard evidence, he walks, all right?
我比谁都想拘捕他，但没确切证据，放他走吧
- So what, nothing turn up at the container yard?
- Team swept every dock.
-难道货场神马都没出现过？
-警队搜遍了每个码头
Found nothing.
啥都没发现
You know why he was thrown
out of the army, Nathan?
你知道那保安为神马不干了吗，雷森？
- He resigned.
- He was guilty.
-他辞职了
-那是他心里有鬼
He witness has retracted. The container
yard is clean and Warns' alibi is solid.
他收回证言，货场被清理了，沃茨在罪案现场是不争的事实
The decision's already
been made, OK?
已经定论了，好吧？
- Well, the decision's bad.
- And so's your attitude.
-呸！这个决定真烂
-注意你的态度哈
Oi, why don't you go and
wait inside, yeah?
嘿，你还是里边等着，好伐？
Go on.
快去
She's good at her job, you know.
她干得不错，你知道
No, I like her. She's got the
same fire that you used to have.
嗯，我挺喜欢她，她有些像你以前
- How can you do that?
- What?
-你干嘛那样？
-哪样？
How can you just stand there
and not even argue your point?
你干嘛傻站在那儿不和他们争辩？
If I had a point, I'd argue it.
如果我有观点的话，我会和丫争辩的
When I asked to work with you, Max,
I thought you'd at least have my back.
我申请跟你工作时，麦克斯，我以为你至少是我的靠山
Yeah, look... Look, I've just
learned not to get involved, all right?
瞧，我已经学会明哲保身啦，好伐？
You've just learned to take it up
the ass from Geiger.
你只学会了擦PP走人
Human emotion, my god.
复杂的人类情感！偶滴神那！
- You want to get yourself a notebook.
- You worried I might get ink poisoning, aren't you?
-你该弄个笔记本啥的啦
-你还知道担心我墨水中毒吗？
- It's already infected your tongue.
- At least my ass is still intact.
-你嘴巴已经中毒啦
-至少俺滴PP还好！
Juka, what's that about?
祖卡，那边啥情况？
Young guy traveling under
the passport of William Morgan.
发现有个年轻人持有威廉 摩根的护照旅行
Collapses on the runway
at city airport.
在机场跑道上被拘
Turns out the real Morgan died five years
ago in a car crash in Dudlowe, Essex.
而真的威廉 摩根五年前在Essex的Dudlowe的车祸中已经挂掉了
- So what?
- So they check his fingerprints.
-然后呢？
-他们验了他的指纹
Turns out that he was arrested
as a kid for shoplifting.
发现他小时候曾在一起商店劫案中被拘过
Juka, come on, man,
my toast is getting cold.
祖卡，快点，伙计，我的面包快凉啦
It's Ruan Sternwood.
那家伙是鲁安 斯坦伍德
All right, I'm being asked a lot of the same questions,
so grab pens 'cause I'm not repeating it.
好哦，我还要问一堆问题，拿上笔，我不会再重复
Last night, Jacob Sternwood's son...
昨晚，雅各布 斯坦伍德的儿子...
Ruan Sternwood was picked up at city airport
suffering from a gunshot wound to the stomach.
鲁安 斯坦伍德在机场被拘，发现其腹部有枪伤
Ballistics show he was shot by
the same gun as Otis Blake, but this...
弹道分析显示他被枪击欧茨 布莱克的同一支枪所伤，但...
...this is the icing.
这也是症结所在
Before Ruan collapsed, he made a call from
a mobile to a landline in Hella, Iceland.
鲁安完蛋前，给冰岛的Hella的一处座机打过一个电话
Right now, an s. F.O. Unit is making its way to a remote
address 94 kilometers east of Reykjavik.
现在，一支特别行动小组正前往冰岛首都雷克雅维克以东94英里处的一个偏远之地
They'll make entry at approximately
2200 hours...
他们已经花费了近2XX小时的时间
...and they've been instructed
to shoot to disable.
他们得到的指令是一定要开枪制服对方
- It won't work.
- Why?
-没用的
-为啥？
Because it won't.
They need to hold off.
-不管用
-他们该停止行动才对
Or let Sternwood think
we haven't clocked on.
或者让斯坦伍德认为我们啥都没干
Surround the house, take him when he
moves, that's when he's vulnerable.
包围那房子，攻击并拘捕他
Max!
麦克斯！
- Say something then.
- No.
-那你来说吧
-没啥说的
Something you want to add, mate?
你想补充点啥么？伙计？
No. No.
不，不
It won't work.
这样不管用的
Uh, all right, um...
呃，好吧，那啥..
Well, what do you think will work...
擦！那你说啥管用..
...Sarah?
莎拉？
Well... Nathan...
呃，雷森...
You've gotta...
你们要...
Hold off, wait,
停下来，等待，
Surround the house and...
包围房子，然后...
Take him when he's least expecting it.
至少像他期待的那样处置他
And if I tell them to hold off...
如果我说他们该延迟一下...
...and we turn up and find out
that he's got away- again-
我们发现他又跑掉了
Who's gonna take the flak? You had no
problem pointing the finger last time.
谁该承担这个责任？你上次就瞎JB搞了一回
You disobeyed orders, you paid the price.
你不守纪律，你己付为此出了代价
If you're such an expert, mMax, why's he still
at large and why is you not standing up here?
如果你真是砖家，麦克斯，为啥他还逍遥法外，为啥你没有站在本尊这个位置？
I don't give a fuck about any of that stuff.
我受够了这些烂事
- Do you know what, mate?
- It's your call.
-你知道么，伙计？
-你的电话
Yeah, it is and it's done.
是啊，就是这样子的，没办法
Max, this is gonna be hard.
Try not to act too smug.
麦克斯，越来越难了，别再清高了
Innocent people were killed last
night. I'm not smug about anything.
昨晚又有无辜的人挂掉了，我才不因任何事清高
You know what I mean.
你知道我指的是啥
Oh, for god's sake, I'm Robert
Wiseman's campaign manager. Max...
看在神的面上，我是罗伯特 魏茨曼的竞选部长，麦克斯...
Tell him who I am. / What? No, I've
never seen her before in my life.
告诉他我是谁。啥？才不，我从没见过她
And we're trying to establish whether
there's a link between the two cases.
我们正尝试将两案关联起来
Right, I'll take any questions you might have.
好吧，我会回答你们任何问题
That's two people in a related shooting
and not a single lead to show for it.
这是相关的枪击案中的两个人，而不是孤立事件
As I said, we're on top of it.
正如我所言，我们正着手调查
I'm confident it will be
resolved quickly and efficiently.
我相信案子会快速而有效地侦破
Thanks.
谢谢
How do you react to the shadow home
secretary's claims that we're suffering twice...
你对影子内阁大臣所称的我们正两次遭受...
...the level of violent crime
committed in the United States?
米国暴力犯罪激增的评论是？
Well, I'm not gonna get
involved in an election campaign.
嗯，我不对任何涉及竞选的问题评论
Suffice to say, whoever takes office on the 21st needs
to ensure the police have all the resources they need...
足以说明，在21世纪任何执政者都需要确保警方拥有所有必要资源...
...to carry out their job. \You think what happened
to Sternwood's son will draw him out?
以执行其任务。
你认为斯坦伍德的儿子要怎样才能撇清关系？
I was shot in the leg, Jane, not in the head.
我那次是被击中腿部，简，不是脑袋坏掉了
Don't I know it.
我似乎明白
Arm transport police with tasers.
装备了泰瑟枪的押运警员
Increasing the number of officers
qualified to utilize firearms.
增加了限制使用火器的警员数目
- Don't ask.
- Wasn't gonna.
-别提问啦
-不是吗？
Next.
下一个问题
Your own figures show a 17% increase
in gun crime in the last 12 months.
你们自己的数据显示过去12个月里涉枪犯罪增加了17%
I'm not gonna get into a debate
about statistics.
我不会为统计数字辩护
If there's no more relevant questions,
I'll bid you all a good morning. Thank you.
如果没有其他相关问题，我要在此祝你们早安啦，谢谢
Tough questions.
都是些刁钻的问题哈
I've heard worse.
我还听过更刁钻的
You ducked them like a pro.
你在回避他们
I'd take that as a compliment...
我只把他们当做抱怨罢了
If you weren't the shadow
home secretary's campaign manager.
要不是你是影子内阁大臣的竞选部长的话
We win this election and you'll get the
backing you need, but for now...
我们早就赢了选举你也会得到你想要的，但是现在
...the questions are gonna get tougher.
问题都更艰难了
Well, I'm sure you'll spin it
to your own agenda.
嗯，我想信你已经安排妥当一切
The kid at the airport, any
truth he's Jacob Sternwood's son?
那个机场里的孩子，真的是雅各布 斯坦伍德的儿子？
- Where did you get that?
- Come on.
-你从哪儿得知的？
-得了吧
I ran your press for five years.
我跟了你五年的新闻记者会啦
Could be useful.
可能会有用的
- If it's handled well.
- Yeah.
-如果处理得当的话
-是
- See you, Jane.
- See you.
-再见，简
-再见
I've got a meeting with the anti
- gun lobby, I've got two minutes.
我要拜会禁枪协会的人，我只有两分钟时间给你
Max and I were just discussing
this Blake case and...
麦克斯和我刚刚讨论过布雷克的案子..
We thought there may be a way through
Ruan Sternwood. Didn't we, max?
我们认为可以利用鲁安 斯坦伍德一下，是么？麦克斯？
Uh, yeah! Look, I don't know
about the Blake case, but...
呃...，那啥，我不懂啥布雷克的案子，但是...
...if it was me, and it's not me, but if it was,
I'd put Ruan in an open hospital, public...
如果是我管的话，但并不由我管，但是如果由我管，我会把鲁安弄到一个公共医院，公开的
...man it 'round the clock, dangle
the hooks, see if Sternwood bites, that's it.
我们的人守候着，亮出这个鱼饵，如果斯坦伍德上钩，就搞定他
- You think you two are up to this?
- Yeah, of course we are.
-你以为你俩能负责这个案子？
-当然我们能
- Aren't we?
- Mm-hmm.
-我们行的对吧？
-呃，嘿
- Max? He's still reeling from last time.
- He was bang on about Iceland, wasn't he?
-麦克斯行吗？他上次中枪现在还是跛的呢
-他不停在念叨冰岛的事儿呢，不是么？
Look, um, I'm up to it, all right?
好吧，呃，我扛上这事儿了，行不？
You leave the Blake case to Nathan and
you stay out of his way, do you understand?
你把布雷克的案子交给雷森，离开他的圈子，明白？
I take your point. You get
the hospital, but that's all.
我替你的位置，你接下医院的活儿，就这样
- Thom, he's too close to it.
- Nathan, fuck off.
-托姆，他有点过了
-滚蛋，雷森
I'm not too close,
I'm just over it.
我不是太过了，我是被挂得太高了
You won't have a problem then, will you?
有啥问题么？
- Do you want me to start on row two?
- No, just start with the "a" class, son.
-你要我按第二方案来吗？
-不，你只执行A方案，儿子那边
Yes, boss.
遵命，头儿
Jesus, jake. Why don't we just let
off some fireworks while we're at it?
天啊，杰克，为嘛我们来时不放点烟花呢？
I wouldn't be here if I wasn't
a thousand percent, you know that.
如果我不是抓住那千分之一的机会的话就不会在这儿了，你明白
Come here.
这边来
- Car was run of the mill?
- It was perfect.
-我的车很差么？
-车很棒！
- Took a few knocks?
- I've had worse.
-受到攻击了？
-更遭
So why did you level the house?
为什么毁了那间屋子？
Became just another
place to hide- I'd rather see it burn.
只是个藏身之地罢了，我宁愿它烧掉
If it's any consolation, you're looking good.
如果需要安慰的话，你看起来还不错
- Great outdoors.
- Mm.
-在户外还不错
-嗯
What's that?
这是啥意思？
Karen says I carry it off.
凯伦说我算躲过一劫
Oh, does she now? Well,
you look like Kenny Rogers.
哦，她也知道了?好吧，你看起来像大胡子歌手Kenny Rogers
Mmm, I can shave and you'll still
look like a bag of smashed crabs.
嗯，我可以刮掉胡子，但你怎么都像一袋烂螃蟹
How is he?
我儿子他怎么样了？
They've taken him to st. Bart's.
他们送他去了伦敦圣巴罗多买医院
And?
然后呢？
Apparently Ruan was involved
in some low-level stuff.
显然弄了些烂人看管着
Nothing serious.
那问题不大
But he started hanging out with
a kid called Otis Blake.
但是他和一个叫欧茨 布雷克的孩子一起出去混
All mouth, no muscle.
赤手空拳
Ruan raised the cash, using the
family name as leverage.
鲁安提高了价码，用了家庭的名字施加影响
Otis did the deals.
欧茨同意成交
And that's where it
gets complicated.
因此事儿变复杂了
Four days ago, Otis was found floating
in the Thames with a bullet in his head.
4天前，欧茨的尸体被发现漂浮在泰晤士河上，头部中枪
The next day, they pick up Ruan at city
airport suffering from a gunshot wound.
第二天，他们在机场捉到了鲁安，腹部中弹
They know who he is, Jake.
你知道他是谁，杰克
They're going to make
an example of him...
他们正拿他做样子...
...because of us.
因为我们
Because of you.
因为你
Eastover Air, Beaverbrook
Chartered, Conlin Museum,
柯林博物馆，比弗布鲁克特许者，伊斯托弗空军
Sherriff Capital, Armourers Pacific, Elite
security, landed armored trucks twice.
谢里夫的大资本家，太平洋舰队军械师，精英保安，两次装甲车空降纪录
He's created a legend for
himself, I'll give him that.
他创造了自己的传奇，我很佩服他的
What?
都是些神马啊？
Man can kidnap, kill, rob...
他可以去绑架，杀戮，抢劫...
...hurt people.
伤害他人
And he gets called a legend.
然后别人称他为传奇
Do well at school, Juka?
Get good marks and all that?
你上学时成绩好吗，祖卡？获得各种好成绩？
- Hmm?
- Yes.
-嗯
-是哦
So you work hard, you do your best.
所以你勤奋工作，尽你所能
And I guarantee you'll get
remembered as a nobody.
我保证你最终碌碌无为
The only lasting thing about Jacob Sternwood
should be his fucking prison sentence.
雅各布 斯坦伍德最终会被绳之以法的
- Do you work here?
- What's that?
-你是工作人员吗？
-怎么啦？
Sorry, mate...
I'm looking for room 45.
抱歉，伙计，我在找45号房间
- Second door on the right.
- Nice one, cheers, mate.
-左边第二个门
-好人呐，伙计，谢啦
Get down!
趴下！
- Fuck are you doing here?
- I'm looking for room 45!
-来这儿干嘛？
-我在找45号房
All right, fuck that,
up you get, come on.
好吧，去你的，起来，快点
- Who fucking sent you?
- No one sent me.
-谁指使你来的？
-没人指使
You're lying to me already!
你已经对我撒谎了哦！
- Max. Max!
- I fucking swear!
-麦克斯！麦克斯！
-正草你呢
- Can I ask you a few questions, sir?
- No, no, it's fine...
-问你几个问题行吗？先生
-不，不，没事儿的
Oi. Who told you that was room 45?
哦，谁TM告诉你那是45号房的?
What? I dunno, some tall geezer
in a baseball cap.
神马？我不知道他是谁，一个戴棒球帽的瘦高老头儿
Move, move!
快！快！
Get down!
趴下！
Max!
麦克斯！
How is he?
他咋啦？
We're not gonna walk him
out of there.
我没能把他弄出来
Lewinsky's all over him.
他被莱温斯基监控着
I told you. You should have killed
that prick when you had the chance.
告诉你，你早该有机会干掉那个条子了
- Do you know the Greigo Mar?
- Yeah, it's a...
-你知道啥是Greigo Mar么？
-知道哦，是...
...a hotel.
一家旅馆
Ruan mentioned it the night he called.
鲁安在昨晚的电话里提到它
It was the last thing he said.
是他说的最后一句话
Take me there.
带我去那儿
Sorry, excuse me.
抱歉，打扰一下
- Excuse me, what's going on?
- He's going into cardiac arrest.
-抱歉，怎么了？
-他心跳要停止了
- What?
- Wait outside.
-啥？
-到外边去
No, if you let this out,
he'll disappear.
不，如果你出去，他就会跑掉的
Oi, you just stuck a gun
in a visitor's face.
我擦！你居然用枪指着游客的脸
- They're trying to kick usout of here.
- All right, all right, look, look.
-他们会把我们踢出这儿的
-好吧，好吧，等下，等下
Just, let me think. Just.. You keep
Sarah and I posted here, all right?
让我想想，你带莎拉走，我守在这儿，好吧？
We keep things ticking over.
咱们悠着点，把事儿办周全
You release that Ruan's improved and
that's going to keep Sternwood in play.
你放风说鲁安好转了，这可能会上斯坦伍德上钩
If he thinks he can walk his son out...
如果他觉得他能把他儿子弄出去的话
...he's going to check the angles.
他就要小心他的小命啦
Thom. Look, at the very least,
汤姆，瞧，至少
It's gonna keep the press off your
back for a couple of more days.
至少可以让你身上的压力减少几天
All right, you stay here.
好吧，你留守这里
Got it all figured out, haven't you?
都计划好了，是吧伙计？
He would have checked in
under his mother's name.
以他老母的名义，他一定会来的
Welcome to Hotel Greigo Mar.
欢迎来到Greigo Mar宾馆
Roy, bring me that penknife.
罗伊，把小刀递给我
What are you thinking?
你想什么呢？
I'm thinking...
You put it out there...
我在想，如果我们把它放在这外面
Ruan Sternwood was staying
at the Greigo Mar Hotel.
假装鲁安 斯坦伍德还在Greigo Mar宾馆的话
And let's see what comes crawling in.
看看会发生什么
Okay.
好
- Can you hide that somewhere safe?
- Yeah.
-你能找个安全的地方藏身吗？
-可以
When you've done that...
你做完这些以后
...go home, kiss your wife.
回家，啵你的傻老婆
Don't get involved in this mess.
再别牵涉进这些烂事儿了
I was involved the second
they pulled the trigger.
我这是第二次啦，是他们先惹出的事儿
I take it we're not staying here.
我假装我们不在这里
You are. I'm gonna go track down this security
guard, see if he's been squared off by Sternwood.
好，我开始追查这个保安，看他是否被斯坦伍德摆平了
What, you think he shot
his own son?
什么？你认为他会射杀自己的儿子？
No, no, I've think he's been
planning something.
不，不，我认为他正在筹划什么阴谋
It fucked up and now
he's covering his tracks.
但是搞砸了，所以现在他要隐藏好他那些痕迹
Can you just take a step back
for a minute?
你能消停几分钟吗？
What the fuck's that
supposed to mean?
那TM意味着什么呢？
Meaning maybe it's not
all about Jacob Sternwood.
意味着这可能不全和斯坦伍德有关
What else is it about?
那会和啥有关？
Dean Warns for a start.
And a dead 22-year-old.
从沃茨 迪安的谋杀开始，一个22岁的年轻人被杀
Yeah, which all lead back
to Jacob Sternwood.
是的，这些都该归咎于雅各布 斯坦伍德
- I've just got to figure out how.
- You?
-我刚刚想出是怎么回事儿了
-你？
Right!
对
You know what? Catching Sternwood
is not going to change the past.
你知道么？捉住斯坦伍德并不会改变过去的什么事儿
It has to!
那是！
Or I'm always gonna be that nobody
that got shot in a tunnel...
我一直想是不是三年前斯坦伍德你没有在隧道里将你枪杀...
...and let him get away with it.
却让你保住小命
- Listen!
- Don't.
-听着！
-才不
- Please..
- Don't.
-求你了
-才不
Listen to me!
听我说！！
What went down in that tunnel...
三年前你如果没有跟进了隧道
...does not make you a nobody.
你不会像现在一样泯然众人
Hey, trust me.
嘿，相信我
Concentrate on now.
集中注意力
'Cause you're too good
at your job to waste it.
因为你太会浪费你的工作了能力了
You're still gonna have to
stay here and cover for me.
你还要守在这里掩护我
Didn't anything I just said
make sense to you?
我刚说的对你有用吗？
I understood it,
just don't agree with it.
我明白，就是不同意你的话
- I'm coming with you.
- Sarah, I am not fucking asking!
-我要跟你去
-莎拉，我没要求你这样
You're staying here.
你就留在这儿
Fuck off.
去你的
It's down to you,
whatever you want.
随你啦，爱去哪儿去哪儿
I mean, you want it
new school or old school?
我的意思是，你想它是新学校式还是旧学校式呢？
We roll it new school, I'll get that shit
on facebook, twitter, BBM. Instant.
去TM的新式，我会把它贴到facebook, twitter, BBM.QQ，马上！
That's the way the gospel's
usually nowadays, cyber-styley.
这就是今天的传福音的方法，网络传道
We go old school, it's more orthodox
methods, people on the pavement.
我们上的是旧学校，这是更传统的方式，人们被遗弃在街上
Bookies, dog tracks, runners,
bit of a nightmare, but I can do it.
业余赌徒，溜 狗的，跑步的，真是梦魇！但是我能搞定
Or I can blitz it on both platforms,
but that's pretty much gonna be double.
可能我可以横贯两个阳台，但是会让我困难加倍
You want me to get rid of
this shit?
你让我从这烂事儿中脱身？
Ruan Sternwood is staying at
the Greigo Mar Hotel...
鲁安斯坦伍德还在Greigo Mar宾馆
...room 1308.
1308房
Just put that out there, okay?
就引他们去那儿，好不？
And Rob...
还有，Rob...
You mess this one up.
你把这事弄糟了
I'll show you
fucking old school.
我会向你展示旧学校的方式的
Joseph Ojogo?
约瑟 欧姜哥？
Right, wait there.
对，请等一下
Did you ever see or hear
a Jacob Sternwood at the container yard?
你听说过货场的雅各布 斯坦伍德么？
- No.
- No?
-没
-没？
Do you never met him?
你从未见过他？
Then what'd you retract your
statement for?
那你为什么要收回你的证词？
You said you were positive you saw Dean Warns
with Otis Blake the night he was killed.
你说过你啃腚在欧茨 布雷克被杀之夜见过沃茨 迪安的
What's changed?
有什么不同么？
All you people look the same.
你的人看起来来都一样
Yeah, look at this.
Go on, look at it.
是，看这个，别走，看看
He'll walk free, do it again,
and that'll be your fault.
他已经获释了，还会再来杀人的，这会是你的错
Look...
看！
...in Nigeria, this is reality.
在尼日利来，这就是现实
- No one gets justice.
- Yeah, and in this country...
-木有人能获得公正待遇
-对，特别在这个郭佳
You'll go to prison for taking bribes
and pretending something didn't happen.
你如果再装聋做哑就会因受贿入监狱
- How's that?
- Please...
-那又如何？
-求你了
I have a family to support, eh?
我木有家庭啊，对不？
A family who I hope to come and
live with me here in England.
我真心希望在英国能有一个心爱的家庭
So what are you saying?
你在说啥捏？
I'm saying, I don't know
this Jacob Sternwood.
我是说，我其实不认识这个雅各布 斯坦伍德
I'm saying when I'm given
a new job..
我的意思是当我有了个新工作
...with more money,
I don't argue.
有更多的银子，我不会介意继续装聋做哑的
- What?
- This may be nothing...
-有情况？
-可能没有价值
All the informants, all of them, called
within the space of half an hour...
所有的信息，所有的，要在半个小时内讲完
...of each other saying exactly the same thing.
别的事也同样要精确地说出来
What thing?
什么事？
They've all heard that Ruan Sternwood is
apparently staying at the Greigo Mar Hotel...
他们都知道了鲁安 斯坦伍德显然待在Greigo Mar宾馆的
...room 1308.
1308房
- Money's not here.
- Keep looking.
-这儿没钱呐
-继续找
Fuck you, Bartnick.
What do you think I'm doing?
我草！巴尼克，你想我在干嘛？
Bartnick!
巴尼克!
Harvey, go!
哈维，快跑！
Get out of there!
跑出去
Sternwood!
斯坦伍德！
- There you go.
- Thank you.
-你去那边！
-谢啦
Hi.
嗨
- Sarah.
- Luke.
-莎拉
-鲁克
- Luke?
- Yeah.
-鲁克？
-干嘛？
Luke, um...
鲁克，那啥
I'm in a lot of trouble.
我有大麻烦了
And I was wondering if
you could help me.
我想你能不能帮帮我
Yeah, yeah, what is it?
当然啦，什么麻烦？
Well, my company's lost this container.
嗯，我们公司丢了个货柜
I was wondering if you
could help me find it.
你能不能帮我找到它
Yeah. Then I'm your logistician.
当然，我就是你的军需官
Well, I was hoping you'd say that.
好，我开心你这么说
- Um, what's the name of the company?
- S.C.I Haulage.
-呃，公司叫啥名？
-S.C.I Haulage.
Alright.
好的
Yeah, if you wanted, we could...
Um, find it together.
好，如果你需要，呃，我们可以一起找嘛
But this is actually one of the largest
container yards in Europe.
这实际上是欧洲最大的货场了
Max knows I'm here.
麦克斯知道我在这儿
Don't do this.
请不要...
This is Sarah Hawks,
leave a message.
我是莎拉 豪克斯，请留言
Sarah, it's Max, call me.
莎拉，我是麦克斯，请回电
Have you ever heard of
someone called Bartnick?
你认识一个叫巴尼克的小子么？
- Who?
- Bartnick.
-哪根葱？
-巴尼克
Nope.
不认识
These two guys, you know,
they scoped the room.
这两个家伙，监视过那房间
The way they fired their guns,
it's like they were trained, you know?
他们射击的方式看起来像是受过训的，看得出来么？
It was all too practiced.
都是训练有素的人啊
Hey, honey.
嗨，甜心
Give me the keys, I want to open up.
把钥匙给我，我要打开它
- Kids go off to school okay?
- Yeah, fine.
-孩子们都上学去，好不？
-好
- Hey, Karen.
- Fuck you, Jake.
-嗨，凯伦
-拍悖杰克
Roy, do you know what? I don't want this shit
in my life again. Do you understand me?
罗伊，你知道些神马么？我不想再有这些烂事了，你能理解偶么？
If it was one of ours, this never
would have happened in the first place.
如果我们其中一个人在，第一次的事儿就不会发生
I'm just hoping that this dead policeman
hasn't got anything to do with you.
我只希望这个死掉的条子和你没任何关系
This government expects brave officers
like Harvey Crown...
政府希望警官们都像哈维 克O一样打了鸡血
...to go into battle armed with
only a whistle and a baton.
只叼着只哨子就冲上去博命
That guy's not dead two minutes, Jane. Already
you're going to use that for your campaign?
那些家伙两分钟内死不了，简，你在选战中用过这招么？
This is for your benefit, Max.
这对你有好处，麦克斯
When he's Home Secretary, you're going to get
the proper tools you need to do your job.
他做国安部长时，你将获得趁手的家伙来干活
And half the people in this city won't be
shit-scared just to walk down the street.
这样一来，半数的居民就不会极度恐慌地走在大街上了
Of all people, I thought you'd
have believed in that.
对大多数人来说，我想你会相信这一点的
Jane, I'm paid to catch
crooks, not... get them elected.
简，我拿薪水是捉坏蛋的，而不是...让其当选
Thom?
汤姆？
Gotta talk to you.
我想和你谈谈
I can't understand why an
officer from clubs and vice...
我不理解为什么一个警官被发现出入夜总会并且
...was found dead in Ruan's hotel room
with a gun in his hand.
拿着手枪死在鲁安的酒店房间里
Yeah, I can't understand
what you were doing there.
是，我也不理解为什么你在这儿
I told you the hospital was
yours and nothing else.
我只是告诉你医院才是你告待的地方，没有别的
- I had information, I acted on it.
- Well, so did Harvey Crown.
-我得到一个消息，我正研究呢
-哈维 克O和你一样
Maybe he was checking out a lead
and needed protection.
或许他查出了点什么并且需要保护
If it was just a routine check, if it was just
a couple of good old boys...
如果只是例行检察，如果只是两个老伙计...
...doing their duty, that's fine.
例行公事，那没啥大惊小怪的
But why two officers from separate divisions
twinning it? Why did one of them run?
但是为什么这两个不同片区警官凑到了一起？为什么其中一个要逃跑？
What do you mean two officers?
你说两个警官是什么意思？
Found that at the hotel.
Nathan's.
在宾馆发现的，这是雷森的眼镜
- Did you know about it, Thom?
- Of course I didn't.
-你知道点什么，汤姆？
-啥都不知道
I've got the press jumping all over me,
我知道新闻发布会对我的指责
I'm trying to run this division,
I don't need this shit as well, do I?
我正试着追查这个片区，我不再需要这些烂事了吗？
Jacob Sternwood was there too.
雅各布 斯坦伍德也在那儿
- Have you got evidence?
- He was there.
-你有证据了么？
-他去过那里
Well, that's not good enough.
好吧，还不够呢
You better get your facts straight.
你最好有直接的证据
I'll look into Nathan and Crown and you focus
on Sternwood, okay, and you get back to me.
我会调查雷森和克O，你注意斯坦伍德，好伐，然后和我会合
Yeah.
是
Max...
麦克斯
It's good to have you back.
有你的支持很好
Kincade Security Solutions,
founded in Switzerland 1942...
1942年在瑞士发现的Kincade安保方案
...by a devout Christian. Get this.
虔诚于基督的心，拿到这个
He used to inscribe biblical verse
on the side of their weapons...
他喜欢在他们的武器侧面刻上圣经的警句
Recently experienced a fall in share prices
which they put down to...
近期股价的狂跌被他们归因于...
...and I quote,".. uncertainty over
U. S. Foreign policy...
我会说，永远别相信米国的外交政策
...and poor visibility on contracts
from the U.K Government. "
英国政府的政策亦不明朗
What about Warns?
沃茨怎么样了？
No record he's ever worked for them
as a military contractor.
没有证据显示他为他们的军队服役过
Then you've got to find a
connection with Sternwood.
那么你就查一下他和斯坦伍德的关系吧
- I've tried, there isn't one.
- Try harder.
-我试过了，啥都查不到
-用心再去查
Has Warns traveled to Iceland
in the last 12 months?
沃茨过去12个月到过冰岛么？
Were any weapons that Sternwood
used in the past Kincade? Come on!
斯坦伍德过去在Kincade保安队中用过什么武器？说吧！
Where the fuck is Sarah?
莎拉TMD去哪儿啦？
Find her, all right, tell her to call me.
Tell her if she's still pissed off...
找到她，好伐？要她打电话给俺。告诉她要是她再生气的话
I've got something
that will cheer her up.
我会有办法逗她开心的
- Oh, Sir?
- What?
-噢，先森？
-什么？
Otis Blake arrested a year
ago for a minor drug offense.
欧茨 布莱克去年曾因轻微贩毒罪被捕
Arresting officer: Harvey Crown.
拘捕他的警官是：哈维 克O
Well done.
干得好
Nathan Bartnick.
雷森 巴尼克
My son got involved with something
he didn't understand.
我的儿子牵涉到了他还不懂的事儿里去了
And he paid the price.
他也付出了代价
He's got a good heart,
unlike ours.
他和我们不同，他内心善良
- You killed Crown.
- You shot my son.
-你杀了克O
-你枪击了我儿子
No.
没有
But I know who did.
但是我知道是谁干的
Look, maybe we should
meet tonight.
瞧，我们今晚碰个面如何？
Talk this through.
把这些事儿谈清楚
- I know a place.
- Where?
-我知道有个地方挺合适
-哪里
A club.
一家夜总会
- You all right, mate?
- We're closed.
-都还好吧，伙计们
-我们快完工了
Yeah... Yeah.
Did you get my message?
是的...是的。你收到我的短信了吗？
Yeah, that's the second time.
That's the second time this week...
是的，第二次了，本周第二次
...you sent me to fix a machine
when it's not broken.
你派我去修理设备，它什么时候好过呢？
Yeah, so what's..
嗨，那么...
I don't give a fuck what kind of-
It's fine mate, it's a balls-up at the office.
你配给我的都是神马破搭档，好伙计？把办公室搞得一团糟的
I don't give a fuck what you said.
Just tell him he's a fucking moron.
我给你的不是你说的那样，告诉他他就是TMD傻瓜
This is Sarah Hawks,
leave a message.
我是莎拉 豪克斯，请留言
Relaxing at a murder scene?
在凶杀现场放松呢？
That's commitment to the
cause, isn't it?
都是因果相联的，不是么？
How did you know I was here?
你怎么知道我在这儿的？
I know everything.
我知天知地
Don't doubt it.
无庸置疑
Night shift reported you here.
值夜班的说你在这儿
I was looking for Sarah.
我在找莎拉
What?
Lovers' tiff?
什么？小两口吵架？
You could say that.
你可以这么说
Do you want to know the real reason
they first asked you...
你知道他们第一次处置你的真实原因吗？
...to head up the Sternwood case?
拨高斯坦伍德的案子？
Not fucking really.
不是的
I dunno, my good looks, my charm?
那不知道了，是因为我长得帅？我妹力四射？
We hadn't been able to get anywhere
near Sternwood for years.
我们有一年不能接近斯坦伍德了
Our incompetence could be passed
off as your inexperience.
我们的无能就像你的纯洁一样
You were so fresh, Max.
你太纯洁啦，麦克斯
I knew you could take a couple of knocks
and keep on running.
我知道你能经受多次打击还能保持激情
You worked harder than any man
that came before you.
你比以前任何人都敬业
I mean, Christ, you nearly
caught him single-handedly.
我的意思是，天啊，你差点单枪匹马就捉到他
And you still had to fight
them to take me back.
你还在还在和他们斗也让我折服
I never thanked you for that.
我从未因此对你心存感激
So when you take him down this time,
you take him down hard, okay?
如果你这次能捉到他，你会狠狠地弄他，是吗？
And I'll make sure the whole
world is watching.
我相信全世界都在看着你
I did something,
something I'm not proud of.
我的确做了点事，我并不以此为豪的事
So you better be right
on this, Max.
所以你最好尽你所能，麦克斯
I tapped Nathan's line.
我窃听了雷森的电话
Someone called him
about the Greigo Mar.
有人打电话给他谈了Greigo Mar宾馆的事儿
Nathan was guarded,
he was paranoid...
雷森被监视了，他有些偏执狂
...couldn't wait to get off
the phone quick enough.
挂断电话就迫不急待了
They're meeting tonight.
他们准备今晚碰面
They're meeting here.
他们在这里碰面
I want you to go and
check it out.
我希望你去查个清楚
Keep it contained, yeah?
掌控大局，好吗？
Yeah.
好的
Call me when it's through, yeah?
完事儿后打电话给我好吗？
Yeah.
好的
Sign here please, sir.
请在此签名，先生
You fucking owe me for this.
你TMD的应该感谢我
I'd say this makes us
fair and square.
我要说，这使得我们公平又坦诚
The first one's in.
第一个人已经进入
Gun's ready to fire.
准备好射击
Fuck!
草！
You take Sternwood, he's unarmed.
你对付斯坦伍德，他没武器
I'll deal with Lewinsky.
我对付莱温斯基
Jake?
杰克？
Move!
Go!
快走！快！
Now take me to my son.
现在带我去见儿子
I've been trying to call you, Max.
I'm glad you turned up.
我试过打电话给你了，麦克斯，很高兴你现身了
- Pete, we'll talk later, yeah?
- Yeah, right.
-彼得，我们稍后再谈，好吗？
-好
I'm taking this man
to see his son.
我将带这人去见他儿子
Give us two minutes, could you?
能给我两分钟吗？
What's this?
这是神马情况？
Get out.
出去！
What the fuck?
怎么回事？
Call for backup! Go!
呼叫支援！快！
Deal with him or I fucking will.
你处置他，我来也行
Just give me one minute.
给我一分钟就行
Walk away, Juka.
走开，祖卡
You have to trust me, this isn't what
it looks like. Just turn around.
你一定要相信我，这看起来没那么简单，都是反的
Please, juka, you're gonna
get hurt. Just walk away.
快点，祖卡，你会受伤的，快跑开
We found her body.
我们发现了她的尸体
We found her body in your bed.
我们发现她的尸体在你的床上
Juka, you armed?
祖卡，你怎么会有武器？
Who killed my son?
谁杀了我儿子？
Was it the police that came to
the hotel looking for money?
那个条子是去宾馆找钱的吗？
The ones in the club?
是这人去的夜总会？
What about that girl?
那女孩是谁？
Who was she?
Was she involved?
她是谁？她也涉案吗？
Why didn't you just kill me
that night?
为什么你那晚不杀了我？
Why didn't you just kill me
in that tunnel?
为什么不在那个隧道干掉我？
For what?
为神马？
Your son and Otis Blake were killed by
an ex-soldier called Dean Warns.
你儿子和欧茨布莱克是被一个叫迪安 沃茨的退役士兵杀掉的
That's the guy that focused
on me at the club tonight.
这是今晚在夜总会监视我的那家伙
He was working with Nathan Bartnick...
他曾和雷森 巴尼克共事
...Harvey Crown, and possibly...
哈维 克O，可能还有...
...possibly Lieutenant Commander
Thomas Geiger.
可能还有汤姆 盖革少校
That girl...
那个女孩...
Sarah, had written
something on her hand:
莎拉，在她手上写了点东西：
PUNCH 1-1-9
庞奇 1-1-9
Now, Dean Warns was seen
at the container yard...
现在，迪安 沃茨被发现出现在货场
...with Otis Blake the night of his murder.
和欧茨 布莱克一起，在他被杀那晚
That place is separated into
three different docks:
那地方被分为三个独立的码头：
Turk, Acorn and The Punch.
And that's what I know.
特克，阿肯和庞奇，这是我了解到的情况
1-1-9 are container coordinates.
1-1-9是货柜的坐标
We used to bring diesel in
off the ships.
我们以前在此用柴油机卸船
We'll end this tonight.
今晚就了结一切吧
And when it's over...
一切结束后
you'll go to prison and I'll be
the one that puts you there.
我亲自将送你进监狱
Nan?
奶奶？
I got your message,
are you all right?
我收到你短信了，你还好吧？
What, you feel ill?
什么，你感觉不好？
Look who's here.
瞧，谁来了
It's your old mates from
the Second Battalion.
你第二营的老伙计
All right, mate?
别来无恙，老伙计？
- It's good to see you.
- There's fresh tea in the pot.
-见到你真高兴
-壶里有新鲜茶叶
Your old nan was just telling us how you
make big money working for some...
老奶奶刚告诉我们如何赚大钱..
...private military contractor.
加入私人武装
- Kincade.
- Yeah, that's it.
-肯凯德
-对，是这样的
Says they pay you straight into
some European bank account...
据说直接支付给你的欧洲账户
...so you don't pay no tax.
所以你不用付税
- No tax.
- That's amazing, mate.
-免税
-很诱人哦，伙计
What sort of thing
they have you do?
那他们让你做什么事儿呢？
Oh, it's, um...
哦，那是，那个...
...Pretty cloak-and-dagger.
- Yeah?
-是精心策划的阴谋
-神马？
- So when'd you turn up?
- Oh, not long ago, darling.
-那你什么时候发现的？
-哦，不久前，亲爱的
They told me not to tell you.
Said you'd get a kick out of it.
他们不让我告诉你，说你会因此深感愉悦的
I wish you had, Nan.
希望如此，奶奶
- I'm busy tonight.
- Come on, mate.
-我今晚很忙
-得了吧，伙计
Come and sit down.
快来坐下
Yeah, why not?
为什么不呢？
What could be more important
than seeing your old squad, darling?
还有什么比见到老战友更重要呢，亲爱滴
That's all right, Iris.
好吧，艾瑞斯
We know how busy Dean's been
keeping himself recently.
我们知道迪安最近有多忙
We were just telling your old nan how
we were the only ones to stick up for you.
我们只是想告诉你老奶奶我们是唯一还支持你的
How we were the only ones
to speak up and voice our disgust...
我们是唯一还在仗义直言，表达不满的
...when they forced early retirement.
当他们被迫提前退休时
You were like a rock.
你还硬得像石头般
Smuggling guns in the coffins
of dead soldiers.
用阵亡士兵的棺材走私枪支
Yeah, you wouldn't be involved in
anything as sordid as that, would you?
是的，你本不想涉入如此肮脏的事情中，是吗？
Let's hope it's all behind us.
希望都过去了
How's your son?
你儿子怎样了？
I hear he's been getting himself
into a bit of stick.
我听说他惹了点小麻烦
Yeah, unfortunately,
Ruan passed away recently.
噢，真不幸，鲁安最近过世了
And that's why we've come
to see Dean.
这是为什么我们必需要见迪安的原因
Take him down to the punch
for a few drinks.
带他去庞奇喝两杯
See our old friend, Thomas Geiger.
见见我们的老朋友，汤姆士 盖革
- So how do we do this?
- Roy's feeling a bit rough.
- 那么我们怎么做呢？
- 罗伊感觉有些不爽呢
I get terrible migraines.
Feels like my head's gonna explode.
我有严重的偏头痛，感觉脑袋要爆炸了
He's gonna stay here
and keep her company.
他要留在这儿，照看他的公司
You don't mind if I stay here
and relax, do you, Iris?
别担心我待在这儿，放松点，行吗，艾瑞斯
'Course I don't,
handsome man like you.
因为我没你帅
Maybe they can watch
Calamity Jane.
也许他们能看看《女侠简恩》
I can make us some more tea.
我再泡点茶去
No, no, no, Iris,
you just stay right there.
不，不，不，待在这儿别动
Dean, what's going on?
迪安，怎么了？
Tt's all right, Nan.
没事儿，奶奶
I'll tell you why I'm
a good soldier.
我会告诉你我的从军威水史
Because of selfless commitment.
因为无私奉献
Otis Blake, Ruan Sternwood...
欧茨 布莱克，鲁安 斯坦伍德...
Harvey Crown, Sarah Hawks...
哈维 克O，莎拉 豪克斯...
...all necessary casualties.
和其他所有必要的牺牲
All necessary fatalities
of this operation.
所有和此次行动有关的死亡
Or maybe we're just
murderers, plain and simple.
我们可能只是平凡的杀手
That's where you're wrong.
这就是你错误的地方
I'm a superior soldier.
我却是超级战神
You're just a hired fucking killer.
你就是TMD雇佣杀手而己
I want to settle things.
我想安排后事
When I close this down...
当所有一切都平息之后
...it'll be because I put the operation
before my own needs.
因为我将此次行动置于个人需求之上
Told you before,
I'm wise to you...
告诉你之前，我希望你...
Max.
麦克斯
You think keeping her hostage as
collateral's gonna force me into a corner.
你以为把她当人质来抵押能逼我就范
But none of you
have been where I have.
但是你们没人去过我去的地方
Seen what I've seen.
看到我见过的一切
None of you have that
selfless commitment.
你们没人能无私奉献
Not one of you possesses
what it takes.
你们没人能掌控一切
To actually put a bullet
in the back of that woman's head.
实际上，把一粒子弹射入我奶奶的后脑吧
It's gonna be all right, Nan.
Just close your eyes.
一切都完了，奶奶，闭上眼睛
- Warns?
- I need you to meet me.
- 沃茨？
- 我要见你
At The Punch...
在庞奇
...tonight at 12.
今晚12点
Kincade want me to move them out.
肯凯特希望我把他们弄走
Lewinsky's getting too close.
莱温斯基已经接近了
This could all explode in our hands.
都逃不出我们的手心
I can't do it, it's too risky for me.
我办不到，对我来说太冒险了
You meet me...
你见我...
Or I'll make sure all this lands
on your fucking head.
还是我确信所有的场景都在你的破脑瓜里
- Why do you need me to come down?
- Just fucking do it!
- 叫我下来干嘛？
- TMD照办就行了
Oh, fuck!
哦，草！
How you doing?
你怎么做?
I can't feel my legs, Jake.
我腿麻了，简
Really?
真的？
Fuck off.
去他娘的
- No, you fuck off!
- Jesus.
- 不，去你娘的
- 天哪
You gonna be all right
staying here?
你留在这儿没事儿吧？
Yeah.
没事
I'm sorry for this, man.
抱歉，伙计
No, no, no, you did good.
You did good.
不，不，不，你干得不错，你干得不错
I'm sorry about your boy.
对你儿子的事儿很抱歉
Yeah.
唉
Ladies and gentlemen, the man who's
going to lead this party into government...
女士们先森们，这位即将带领政党入主政府的先生
...our friend, our leader, Henry Callaghan.
我们的盆友，我们的领袖，亨利 卡拉汉
You're a very difficult woman
to track down all of a sudden.
你真是追踪突发事件的难缠的女人
It's a very busy time for me.
这是我的艰难时刻
Warns wants to meet me tonight.
沃茨今晚想见我
At The Punch.
在庞奇
Who arranged this, was it you?
Kincade?
谁安排的？是你吗，还是肯凯特？
Thought you had everything you needed.
All the headlines you require, am I right?
考虑你的所有收获，你要的所有头条新闻，不是吗？
Janie, you listening to me?
简，在听我说吗？
Your little project came
apart at the seams.
你的小阴谋开始偏离轨道了
Max is an inch away from piecing
all this together...
麦克斯很快就会将所有线索联系到一起了
...and Sternwood is still at large,
so you better pay attention.
斯坦伍德仍然在逃，你最好小心点
Campaign's going very well.
选战进行的很顺利
We're ahead in the polls, if that's
what you're referring to, Thom.
我们的选票已经领先了，这是你希望得到的，汤姆
No, it's not what I'm referring to.
不，这不是我想要的
Who arranged tonight?
今晚的见面是谁安排的？
- You've lost me, I'm afraid.
- You fuckin' bitch!
- 你恐怕已经失去我了
- 臭婊子！
People have died because of this...
Because of us.
很多人们因此而亡，因我们而亡
I've lost men all because of
your fucking progress...
我因为你TMD进步失去了好多兄弟
...and you sit there in denial
like some fucking royalty..
你还坐在你的王位上人模狗样的矢口否认
...you don't even have the class
to look me in the eye.
你甚至没有把我放在眼里
Thom, listen.
汤姆，听我说
I have to get this speech right with Robert.
我必需要让罗伯特做这个演讲
I think you did the right thing.
我想你做得事情都是正确的
I hope this pans out
for you, okay?
我希望这是你的成功，好吗？
Sorry to call you on this number.
But Warns can't be reached.
抱歉打你这个号码，因为沃茨来不了了
It seems we've got a serious problem.
看样子我们有了大麻烦
You broke my fucking arm!
你伤了我的胳膊！
Thom. Thom.
汤姆！汤姆！
You tell me what the fuck this is.
告诉我这是怎么回事
Don't make things worse
for yourself, Max, eh?
别再把事情弄大了，麦克斯，好不？
You stop this now
and we can settle it.
你现在停下来，我们会安排好一切的
You can't settle the death of Sarah.
你不能安排莎拉挂掉
You can't settle trying to
set me up for murder.
你不能试图安排陷害我做凶手
I am your commanding officer. Right now
you're wanted for the murder of your partner,
我是你的长官，现在你企图谋害你的同事
...so you're going to need all the...
所以你要求
Those two boys...
这两个孩子
...came here on the night of the seventh.
To buy guns from him.
17号那晚来这里买枪
He was with Bartnick and Crown.
他们和巴尼克和克O碰头交易
And one of the boys, Blake,
recognized Crown...
其中一个孩子，布莱克，认出了克O
...he'd been arrested by him a year ago.
他曾在一年前拘捕过他
And that compromised the deal.
这一点使交易起了变故
Blake died, but Ruan got away
with a hold-all full of money.
布莱克死了，但是鲁安跑掉了，带着一个装满钱的旅行包
You get your fucking
hands off me!
把你的脏手拿开！
Bartnick and Crown went to the
hotel looking for their money.
巴尼克和克O回到宾馆找他们的钱
They come across Sternwood.
他们遇到了斯坦伍德
And you suddenly get worried that
I'm gonna piece things together.
你突然担心我会把线索都联系起来
You, Thom, were meant
to be my friend.
你，汤姆，名义上是我的朋友
This can't just be about money.
这不仅仅是关乎钱的事儿
Not for you.
要不是因为你
Policemen weren't meant to die.
那些警官也不会死
It was all gonna be simple.
一切都变简单了
It was gonna change things,
make things better for us.
它会改变一切，让一切都对我们有利
Robert Wiseman, he got it.
罗伯特 魏茨曼，他赢了选战
Just... one more gun scandal and
his party would win the next election.
就因为...越多枪案丑闻，他的党派越易赢得选战
Jane Badham?
简 贝德翰？
She found Warns.
她发现了沃茨
He shipped in the guns,
set up Otis and Ruan as buyers.
他用船运来了枪，设下圈套让欧茨和鲁安来买
I provided some manpower,
turned a blind eye, you know.
我只是提供了些人手，故意视而不见，你懂的
Then a new squad would come in...
然后一支巡逻小队路过
...arrest the two boys
with the guns.
拘捕了那两带枪的小子
Big public outcry,
Jane handles the PR...
公开宣扬此事，然后简操控了公关...
...and Wiseman takes
the next election.
魏茨曼利用这个丑闻赢了接下来的选举
Kincade supplied Warns.
肯凯特公司让沃茨进行了谋杀
Kincade'd get the multi-million-pound
contract to supply body armor...
肯凯特得到了几百万镑的合同支持私人武装
...training packages and guns to the police.
训练包和警用枪械
Yeah.
是的
What do you get, Thom?
你得到了什么，汤姆？
What'd you get?
你得到了什么？
You get a healthy bank account?
你得到了一个安全账户？
Get fast-tracked to the role
of... What?
得到了一个成为什么人物的绿色通道？
Commissioner?
总长？
All for obedience in the line
of fucking duty!
都TMD是为了所谓的恪尽职守！
Fuck off!
去你娘的！
You, more than anyone, should get
what's happening here, Max.
你，本比别人都有资格，得到这一切，麦克斯
I'm the one has to go and see Coppers'
families when they've been shot...
我要去看望那些被害警员的家人
...and murdered in the street 'cause
they haven't gotthe proper armor!
那些被射杀在街上的人，因为他们手里没有足够的自卫武器
What do you think's gonna happen, Max, eh?
You think we're just gonna walk out of here?
你觉得会发生什么事，麦克斯，呃？你觉得我们能走出这儿吗？
Kincade have got all
the bases covered, you know?
肯凯特已经包围了整个基地，你知道吗？
All this means too much to them.
这对他们而言轻而易举
And Warns, eh?
那沃茨呢？
He's not just some fucking
amateur you just walk all over.
他才不是你刚才击败的那些菜鸟呢
You shouldn't have
brought him here, Max.
你根本不该带他来这里，麦克斯
You shouldn't have fucking
brought him here.
你根本不该带他来这里
Get to the car!
I'll cover!
上车，我掩护你们
Let me have your gun.
把你枪给我
Selfless commitment.
让你见识一下神马是无私奉献
Think what he did to you, Max.
想想他怎么对你的，麦克斯
Remember who helped you
come back, huh?
想想谁帮你回到原来的位置的？
You owe me.
你欠我的
This is your chance, Max.
这是你的机会，麦克斯
You bring him in.
是你带他进来的
- You bring that fucker in.
- Enough!
- 是你带那个杂碎进来的
- 够了
- Clear!
- On me!
- 安全
- 跟着我
I don't have visual.
未发现异常
☆土狼☆2325☆基于英文字幕翻译，转载请注明